flowers.vg 2014-11-02

# Privacy Policy

**

"FLOWER PICTURES" displays ads for other websites,   
Each advertiser has their own privacy policy. Please view their individual privacy policy, as it may differ from "FLOWER PICTURES".

**

Personal information about visitors to "FLOWER PICTURES" such as your name, email address, phone, etc. are not collected by "FLOWER PICTURES". 

This site uses the services for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, collects anonymous data typically through the use of cookies. . 

The following anonymous data are collected:   visitor's country, language, browser version, operating system, screen resolution, color palettes, plug-ins, ISP, Java capabilities,  how the visitor got to "FLOWER PICTURES" (bookmark, referring link, email link, etc..), visitor frequency, and other similar data.

Information collected from "FLOWER PICTURES" surveys, mailing list, etc.. are also used for demographic info, and design. 

Below is a few examples how demographic info is released from "FLOWER PICTURES".

****

**Browser Type**

| 

**Microsoft Internet Explorer**

| 

64 %  
  
---|---  
  
**Netscape Navigator**

| 

34 %  
  
**Other**

| 

1 %  
  
**OS Type**

**Windows NT**

| 

4 %  
  
---|---  
  
**Windows 95 and higher**

| 

90 %  
  
**Windows 3.1 and lower**

| 

2 %  
  
**Macintosh**

| 

1 %  
  
**Unix**

| 

1 %  
  
**Other**

| 

2 %  
  
**Domain Type**

**.com**

| 

40 %  
  
---|---  
  
**.edu**

| 

2 %  
  
**.org**

| 

1 %  
  
**.net**

| 

37 %  
  
**.mil**

| 

1 %  
  
**other**

| 

18 %  
  
If you do NOT want this type of data to collected, or if you are concerned about your privacy, there are many anonymous software programs that do not allow data collecting from websites. There are also many security software programs that can protect your privacy. In my opinion the best Security/Privacy software program is "Norton Internet Security 2005." Norton's Internet Security software has Pop-Up controls, Privacy Control, & Security Control. Norton's Internet Security can be purchased from your local computer software store or their website.

There are also many FREE software programs provided by some major search/internet providers that help protect your privacy with pop-up blockers. 

If you have any concerns or questions about "FLOWER PICTURES" Privacy Policy email [webmaster@flowers.vg](mailto:webmaster@flowers.vg)

"FLOWER PICTURES" WORKS WITH A THIRD PARTIES THAT SERVES ADS TO THIS SITE.   

"FLOWER PICTURES" displays ads for other websites,   
Each advertiser has their own privacy policy. Please view their individual privacy policy, as it may differ from "FLOWER PICTURES".

For ads displayed from Google, their policy is listed below  

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
